Guide to the Witchcraft and possession-related movie posters, lobby cards, and other cinema memorabilia, 1916-2015.
Witchcraft and possession-related movie posters, lobby cards, and other cinema memorabilia,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Witchcraft and possession-related movie posters, lobby cards, and other cinema memorabilia, 1916-2015.
4781
57 mapcase folders.
3 cubic feet.
Posters, advertisements, and printed material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Movie posters and other advertisements for films involving witches, witchcraft, possession, devil worship and similar subjects.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Movie posters and other advertisements for films involving witches, witchcraft, possession, devil worship and similar subjects. The films are often of a "cult movie" nature from the United States and Europe with a few from Asia and Africa. Also includes other advertisements and mass market materials involving witches including two political T-shirts from 2010, one concerning the Delaware Tea Party (showing a witch stirring a cauldron-sized cup of tea) and one depicting Senate candidate Christine O'Donnell as a witch.
SUBJECTS
Names:
O'Donnell, Christine.; Čech, Vladimír; Rouleau, Raymond; Lee, Christopher, 1922-2015; Cushing, Peter, 1913-1994 Day-Lewis, Daniel; O'Donnell, Christine; Addams, Charles, 1912-1988.; Delaware Tea Party (Political organization)
Subjects:
Witches; Witchcraft; Witches in motion pictures.; Political culture -- United States.; Political campaigns -- United States.; Women in popular culture -- United States.; Advertising -- Motion pictures -- United States.; Advertising -- Motion pictures; Political campaigns; Political culture; Witches; Witches in motion pictures; Witches in motion pictures; Witchcraft; Magic
Places:
United States
Form and Genre Terms:
Posters.; T-shirts.; Pictorial works
INFORMATION FOR USERS
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Posters arranged chronologically then alphabetically by the original title of the film (according to IMDb) so that all the posters for the same film are kept together. Original title as well as other release titles also given.
SERIES LIST
Series I. 1900-1949
Series II. 1950-1959
Series III. 1960-1969
Series IV. 1970-1979
Series V. 1980-1989
Series VI. 1990-1999
Series VII. 2000-2009
Series VIII. 2010-2018
CONTAINER LIST
- 1900-1949
  - Pear’s Soap, 1900-02 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Tag line: “This Only Is the Witchcraft I have Us’d”
    United Kingdom
    Advertisements
  - Witchcraft, 1916; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Reicher, Frank, 1875-1965
    United States
  - The Witch of the Mountains, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Horkheimer, E.D.
  - A Bargain with Satan, 1913; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Alternate title: The Student of Prague
    Original German title: Der Student von Prag
  - Venchal ikh Satana, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Married by Satan
    Russia
    Devil
    Satanism
    Posters
  - Maid of Salem, 1937; 17 items (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Film stills
  - Maid of Salem, 1937 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Additional information: Grand Theatre Dell Rapids, South Dakota March 15 16 17
    Lloyd, Frank
  - Wizard of Oz, 1939 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - I Married a Witch, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Clair, Ren, 1898-1981
  - I Married a Witch, 1942 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - I Married A Witch, 1942; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Meine Frau die Hexe, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    I Married a Witch
    Germany
    Programs (documents)
  - Meine Frau die Hexe, 1949 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Vredens Dag, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Day of Wrath
    Dreyer, Carl Theodor, 1889-1968
    Denmark
  - La Bruja, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Original Chech title: Diva Bara
    Čech, Vladimír
    Cuba
    Lobby cards
  - La Bruja, 1949 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Diva Bara, 1949 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Title given is the original. Language of the poster is Russian.
    Cech, Vladimir
    Ukraine
  - Black Magic, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Ratoff, Gregory, 1897-1960
- 1950-1959
  - Angel del Infierno, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Mexico
  - Me Enamore de una Bruja, 1958; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Original U.S. title: Bell, Book and Candle
    Spain
  - Bell, Book and Candle, 1958; 2 copies (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Magic
  - Una Strega in Paradiso, 1958 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Italy
    Locandina posters
  - Curtiss Candy Company, 1950-1959; "No tricks with Curtiss treats" and image of a little girl dressed as a witch. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Advertisments
  - La Bruja de la Selva, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Original U.S. title: The Disembodied
    Cults
  - Die Hexe von Montmartre, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Film without actual witches
    Original French title: Gibier de Potence (1950)
    Richeb, Roger, 1897-1989
  - Die Hexe, 1954; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Le Jugement de Dieu, 1952 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Flemish title: Het Godsoordeel
    Grinsson
    Belgium
  - Le Jugement de Dieu, 1952 (Mapcase-folder 57)
    Judgment of God
    France
  - La Strega del Rodano, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Original French title: Le Jugement de Dieu
  - Lois Lane featuring the Witch of Metropolis, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Date of the original comic book is 1958. Postcard was printed in 2010.
    Postcards
  - Meine Schwiegermutter, die Hexe, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Original U.S. title: The Mating Season (1951)
  - I Misteri della Magia Nera, 1958 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Original Mexican title: Misterios de la Magia Negra
    Black magic
  - Misterios de la Magia Negra, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Herr Satan Persnlich, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Original U.S. title: Mr. Arkadin, aka Confidential Report
    Welles, Orson, 1915-1985
    Austria
  - The Undead, 1957 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Original U.K. title: Night of the Demon
    Corman, Roger, 1926-
  - La Femme Nue et Satan, 1959 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    The Head; A Head for the Devil
    Original German title: Die Nackte und der Satan
  - La Noche del Demonio, 1957 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Original U.S. title: Night of the Demon
  - Gefhrlich Sind die Hellen Nchte, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Rare, early Finnish horror film
    The Witch
    Original Finnish title: Noita Palaa Elmn
  - The Witch, 1952 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Finland
  - Sleeping Beauty, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Original animation production drawing of witch Maleficent
    Pencil drawings
  - La Belle aux Bois Dormant, 1959; 4 items (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Malificent the witch in Disney animated feature.
    Original U.S. title: Sleeping Beauty
  - La Sorcire, 1956 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Hebrew
    The Blonde Witch, aka The Sorceress
    Rouleau, Raymond
  - La Sorcire, 1956 (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - The Blonde Witch, 1956; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 3)
    French/Italian/Swedish co-production
    The Sorceress
    Original French title: La Sorcire
    Netherlands
  - Totò all’Inferno, 1955; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Toto in Hell
  - El Idolo de Oro, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Original U.S. title: Voodoo Woman
    Voodoo
  - La Sociere Blanche, 1953 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Original U.S. title: White Witch Doctor
  - The Crucible, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Jean Paul Sartre adaptation of Arthur Miller’s play The Crucible
    Original French title: Les Sorcires de Salem
    Newspaper clippings
  - Die Hexen von Salem, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Die Hexen von Salem, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Witches of Salem, 1956; 7 items (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Film negatives
  - Witches of Salem, 1956; 8 (only have 4) items (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Les Sorcires de Salem, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Les Sorcires de Salem, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Les Sorcires de Salem, 1956 (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Veštice iz Salema, 1956 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Yugoslavia
  - Veštice iz Salema, 1956 (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Die Hexen von Salem, 1956 (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Witches Tales #15, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    U.S. original cover production art
    Simon, Joe
    Book covers
  - Yamba, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Mexico/Cuba/U.S. production
    Cry of the Bewitched
    French title: Yambao, Fille de Satan
    Possession
- 1960-1969
  - Atacan las Brujas, 1968; 3 items (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Santo in the Witches Attack; Santo Attacks the Witches
  - Blue Demon Contra el Poder Satnico, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Blue Demon vs. the Satanic Power
    Window cards
  - Blue Demon Contra el Poder Satnico, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Blue Demon vs. el Poder Satnico, 1966; half sheet (Mapcase-folder 5)
  - Witch Without a Broom, 1968 (Mapcase-folder 6)
    Original Spanish title: Una Bruja Sin Escoba
  - Witch Without a Broom, 1968 (Mapcase-folder 9)
  - Burn Witch, Burn, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Spanish title: Arde Bruja, Arde
  - Burn, Witch, Burn, 1962 (Mapcase-folder 5)
  - La Notte delle Streghe, 1962 (Mapcase-folder 6)
    Original U.K. title: Burn, Witch, Burn
  - La Notte delle Streghe, 1962; 4 items (Mapcase-folder 6)
  - Terror Sexo y Brujeria, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Original Mexican title: Cautivo del mas Alla
  - Hotel de Horrores, 1960 (Mapcase-folder 7)
    Original U.K. title: City of the Dead
    Argentina
  - Die Stadt der Toten, 1960 (Mapcase-folder 9)
    Original U.K. title: The City of the Dead
  - La Cripta del Terror, 1964; 3 items (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Crypt of the Vampire
    Spirit possession
  - Altar de Sangre, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Original U.K. title: Curse of the Crimson Altar
  - Black Horror—Le Messe Nere, 1968; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 4)
  - Black Horror—Le Messe Nere, 1968; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 7)
  - La Maison Ensorcele, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 29)
  - Vood... Los Muertos Vivos, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Original U.S. title: The Dead One; a.k.a Blood of the Zombie
  - Il Demonio, 1963; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 4)
    The Demon
    Exorcism
  - The Devil's Bride, 1968; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Original U.K. title: The Devil Rides Out
    Craven, Wes
  - The Devil's Bride, 1968; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Les Vierges de Satan, 1968 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Devil's Bride
  - La Fiance du Diable, 1968 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Devil's Bride; Flemish title: De Uitverkobene Van de Duivel
  - The Devil's Bride, 1968; 2 copies (Mapcase-folder 7)
  - The Devil's Hand, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - La Mano del Diablo, 1961; 2 items (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Original U.S. title: The Devil's Hand
  - The Devil’s Hand, 1961 (Mapcase-folder 7)
  - Devil's Partner, 1961; 6 items (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - El Demonio Sanguinario, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Original U.S. title: Devil's Partner
  - Devil's Partner, 1961 (Mapcase-folder 7)
  - Le Diable et les 10 Commandements, 1962 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Devil and the 10 Commandments
  - The Devil and the 10 Commandments, 1962 (Mapcase-folder 7)
    Original French title: Le Diable et les 10 Commandements
  - The Devil's Eye, 1960 (Mapcase-folder 7)
    Original Swedish title: Djvulens ga
    Bergman, Ingmar, 1918-2007
  - Davlovo Oko, 1960 (Mapcase-folder 5)
  - Dr. Satan, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Original Mexican title: Doctor Satn
    Morayta, Miguel
  - Dr. Satn y la Magia Negra, 1968 (Mapcase-folder 8)
  - Les Filles du Diable, 1964 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    The Topless War
    Original Flemish title: Duivelse Meisjes;Original Italian title: La Guerra dei Topless;Donne e Diavoli
  - Embrujada, 1969 (Mapcase-folder 8)
    Brazil/Argentine co-production
    Bewitched
  - La Endemoniada, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    A Woman Possessed
  - La Endemoniada, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - La Endemoniada, 1968 (Mapcase-folder 8)
  - El Espejo de la Bruja, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    The Witch's Mirror
  - Espiritismo, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Spiritism
  - Eye of the Devil, 1966; 3 items (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Filming location: Chteau de Hautefort, Dordogne, France
    Original U.K. title: Eye of the Devil
    Tate, Sharon, 1943-1969
  - Eye of the Devil, 1966 (Mapcase-folder 8)
  - Cerimonia per un Delitto, 1966 (Mapcase-folder 5)
  - Cerimonia per un Delitto, 1966; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 5)
  - The Devil's Wanton, 1962 (Mapcase-folder 7)
    1962 re-rerelease of 1949 film
    Prison
    Original Swedish title: Fngelse
  - The Haunted Palace, 1963; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Curse
    Secret rites
    Black mass
  - La Citt dei Mostri, 1963; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Original U.S. title: The Haunted Palace
    Alternative Italian title: Dei Seguaci di Satana
  - La Citt dei Mostri, 1963; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 4)
  - Il Paradiso e L'inferno, 1969; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Heaven and Hell
    Original German title: Himmel og helvete
  - Posesin Satnica, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Original U.S. title: The Innocents
  - The Innocents, 1961 (Mapcase-folder 8)
  - La Sorcire Sanglante, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    The Long Hair of Death
    Original Italian title: I Lunghi Capelli della Morte
  - The Witch's Curse, 1963; 4 items (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Original Italian title: Maciste all’Inferno
  - Maciste en Enfer, 1962 (Mapcase-folder 8)
    The Witch’s Curse
  - The Witch's Curse, 1963 (Mapcase-folder 6)
  - The Witch's Curse, 1963 (Mapcase-folder 9)
  - Gier Nach Blut, 1960 (Mapcase-folder 8)
    Original U.S. title: Macumba Love
  - Black Sunday, 1960 (Mapcase-folder 7)
    Original Italian title: La Maschera del Demonio
  - Black Sunday, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Majka Jovana Andeoska, 1961 (Mapcase-folder 6)
    Mother Joan of the Angels
    Original Polish title: Matka Joanna od aniolw
    Poland
  - Djed Mraz, 1965 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Frosty; Jack Frost; The Crystal Star; Father Frost
    Original Soviet title: Morozko (Морозко)
  - The Naked Witch, 1961 (Mapcase-folder 8)
  - The New Yorker, 1963-11-02; Image of witches on the cover. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Magazines
  - Pasin Oculta, 1967 (Mapcase-folder 8)
    Peruvian/Mexican co-production
    Peru
  - Rosemary's Baby, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Rosemary's Baby, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Pressbooks
  - Rosemary's Baby, 1968 (Mapcase-folder 6)
  - Satan's Sadists, 1969 (Mapcase-folder 6)
    Satan's Sadists
  - Satan’s Sadists, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 26)
    United States Production
  - Satan's Sadists, 1974; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 34)
  - Snow White, 1965 (Mapcase-folder 9)
    Original German title: Schneewittchen und die sieben Zwerge
  - Sfida al Diavolo, 1963; 3 items (Mapcase-folder 6)
    Alternate title: Katarsis
  - Il Lago di Satana, 1966 (Mapcase-folder 6)
    U.K./Italian co-productions
    Original U.S. title: She Beast
  - Il Lago di Satana, 1966; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 4)
    U.K./Italian co-production
  - Jack y la Bruja, 1967 (Mapcase-folder 8)
    Jack and the Witch
    Original Japanese title: Shônen Jakku to Mahô-tsukai (少年ジャックと魔法使い)
  - Il Killer di Satana, 1967; 2 panel poster (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Original U.K. title: The Sorcerers
  - Los Brujos, 1967 (Mapcase-folder 9)
  - The Witch, 1966 (Mapcase-folder 9)
    From the novel by Carlos Fuentes.
    Original Italian title: La Stregha in Amore
    Fuentes, Carlos
  - La Stregha in Amore, 1966; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 4)
  - Le Streghe, 1967 (Mapcase-folder 6)
    The Witches
  - Die Hexe und der Zauberer, 1963 (Mapcase-folder 9)
    Witchcraft in Disney animated feature.
    Original U.S. title: The Sword in the Stone
  - The Witch from Beneath the Sea, 1962 (Mapcase-folder 9)
    Original release: 1958
    Original Brazilian title: Tumulto de Paixes
  - Witchcraft, 1964; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Witchcraft, 1964; 6 sheets (Mapcase-folder 4)
  - Witchcraft, 1964; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 10)
  - Brujerias, 1964 (Mapcase-folder 10)
    Original U.K. title: Witchcraft
  - Bajo la Sombra del Infierno, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    The Devil's Own
    Original U.K. title: The Witches
    Witches' Coven
  - Devil's Own, 1967; 2 items (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Chasseur de Sorcires, 1968 (Mapcase-folder 6)
    Original U.K. title: Witchfinder General
    Witch Trials
  - Cuando Arden las Brujas, 1968 (Mapcase-folder 9)
  - Las Brujas del Infierno, 1969; 3 items (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Original U.S. title: The Witchmaker;The Legend of Witch Hollow, Witchkill
  - The Witchmaker, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    The Legend of Witch Hollow, Witchkill
  - The Witchmaker, 1969 (Mapcase-folder 10)
  - The Legend of Witch Hollow, 1969; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 10)
    Original U.S. title: The Witchmaker; Witchkill
  - Devil Fighter, 1969 (Mapcase-folder 10)
    Original Taiwanese title: Zhuo yao zhan mo
    Thailand
- 1970-1979
  - A-G
    - Abby, 1974; 2 items (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Spanish title: Seduccion Diabolica
      Blaxploitation
    - Abby, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 11)
    - Abby, 1974; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 28)
      Abby
    - Alucarda, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Sister’s of Satan aka Alucarda, Innocents from Hell, Mark of the Devil 3
    - Alucinaciones, 1976 (Mapcase-folder 11)
    - L’Amante del Demonio, 1972; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 28)
      The Devil's Lover (theatrical release); Lucifera: Demonlover (DVD release)
    - L’Amante del Demonio, 1972; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 28)
    - Las Amantes del Diablo, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 11)
      Feast for the Devil; Feast of Satan; Night of the Devils
    - I Diabolici Convegni, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 23)
      Original Spanish title: Las Amantes del Diablo
    - I Diabolici Convegni, 1971; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 28)
    - I Diabolici Convegni, 1971; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 28)
      Feast of Satan
    - La Maison du Diable, 1979 (Mapcase-folder 23)
    - Witchcraft '70, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Original Italian title: Angeli Bianchi... Angeli Neri
      Pagain rituals
    - Angeli Bianchi…Angeli Neri, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 23)
      Witchcraft '70
    - Sorcellerie, Magie et Messes Noires, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 23)
      Scattini, Luigi, 1927-2010
    - Sorcellerie, Magie et Messes Noires, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 23)
    - Sorcellerie, Magie et Messes Noires, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 28)
    - El Anticristo, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 11)
      Original Spanish title: L'Anticristo
    - The Tempter, 1978 (Mapcase-folder 11)
    - De Antikrist, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 23)
      The Antichrist.
    - L'Anticristo, 1974; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 28)
      The Antichrist; Blasphemy; The Tempter
    - The Astrologer, 1977 (Mapcase-folder 11)
    - Asylum of Satan, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Audrey Rose, 1976 (Mapcase-folder 11)
    - Audrey Rose, 1976; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 28)
    - Audrey Rose, 1976; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 28)
    - Exorcismo de Amor, 1973; 2 items (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Original Italian title: Baba Yaga
    - Land of the Minotaur, 1976; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Original U.K. title: The Devil's Men
    - The Devil's Widow, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Original U.K. title: The Ballad of Tam Lin;The Devil’s Woman
    - The Devil's Widow, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 14)
    - La Viuda del Diablo, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 14)
      The Devil's Widow
    - Sapore di Donna, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 24)
    - La Bruja Novata, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 12)
      Original U.S. title: Bedknobs and Broomsticks
    - Exorcismus - Cleo, la Dea dell'Amore, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 23)
      Original U.K. title: Blood from the Mummy's Tomb
    - Blood on Satan’s Claw, 1971; 2 copies (Mapcase-folder 12)
      U.K. Production
    - In den Krallen des Hexenjgers, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 12)
      Original U.K. title: Blood on Satan's Claws
    - La Pelle di Satana, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 23)
      Original U.K. title: Blood on Satan’s Claw
    - La Pelle di Satana, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 23)
      Blood on Satan's Claws
    - Blood Orgy of the She Devils, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 12)
    - Brotherhood of Satan, 1971; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Brotherhood of Satan, 1971; 16 items; 8 color, 8 black and white (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Brotherhood of Satan, 1971; 3 (2) sheets (Mapcase-folder 12)
    - Brotherhood of Satan, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 28)
    - Byleth: Il Demone dell’Incesto, 1972; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 28)
      Demonic possession
    - Cartas de Amor a una Monja, 1977 (Mapcase-folder 12)
      Franco, Jess
    - Child's Play, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 12)
    - The Devil Within Her, 1974; 7 items (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Beyond the Door
      Pregnancy
      Devil's Baby
    - Beyond the Door, 1974; 3 items (Mapcase-folder 11)
      Original Italian title: Chi Sei?; U.K. title: The Devil Within Her
    - The Devil Within Her, 1976 (Mapcase-folder 16)
    - I Don’t Want to Be Born, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 16)
    - Chi Sei?, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 23)
      U.K. title: The Devil Within Her
    - Chi Sei?, 1974; 6 items (Mapcase-folder 23)
    - Diabolica, 1974; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 23)
      Japan
    - Quin Eres, 1974; 4 items (Mapcase-folder 23)
    - Beyond the Door II, 1978; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 11)
    - Kratka noć leptira, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 23)
      Short Night of the Glass Dolls
      Original Italian title: Corta Notte delle Bambole di Vetro
    - Locura, 1974; 12 items (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Original U.K. title: Craze
    - Il Buio Macchiato di Rosso, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 12)
      Original US title: Craze
    - Craze, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 13)
    - Il Buio Macchiato di Rosso, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 23)
    - Il Buio Macchiato di Rosso, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 29)
    - Cristiana Monaca Indemoniata, 1972; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 29)
      Our Lady of Lust
    - Cristiana Monaca Indemoniata, 1972; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 29)
    - La Cruz del Diablo, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 13)
    - Cry of the Banshee, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 13)
    - Der Todesschrei der Hexen, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 13)
      Original U.K. title: Cry of the Banshee
    - Der Todesschrei der Hexen, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 13)
    - Satana in Corpo, 1971; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 29)
    - Damien: Omen II, 1978; 2 copies (Mapcase-folder 13)
    - Damien: Omen II, 1978; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 29)
    - Dark August, 1976 (Mapcase-folder 13)
    - Daughters of Satan, 1972; 8 items (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Die Nonnen von Clichy, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 14)
      France/Portugal co-production
      She-Demons
      Original French title: Les Dmons
    - L’Isola delle Demoniache, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 29)
      Curse of the Living Dead
      Original French title: Les Demoniaques
    - Demon Lover, 1976 (Mapcase-folder 13)
    - Rose Rosse per il Demonio, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 24)
      Original U.K. title: Demons of the Mind;Blood Evil;Blood Will Have Blood;Nightmare of Terror
      Satanic Possession
    - Les Démons de l’Esprit, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 26)
      Flemish title: De Rode Kamers van de Geest
      Original U.K. title: Demons of the Mind;Blood Evil;Blood Will Have Blood;Nightmare of Terror;Flemish title: De Rode Kamers van de Geest
    - Rose Rosse per il Demonio, 1972; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 29)
    - Der Teufel in Miss Jonas, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 21)
      The Devil in Miss Jones
    - The Devils, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 14)
    - I Diavoli, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 29)
      Original U.K. title: The Devils
    - The Devil’s Garden, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 24)
    - The Devil's Rain, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 14)
    - La Pluie du Diable, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 14)
      The Devil's Rain
    - Il Maligno, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 24)
    - Devil Woman, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 14)
      Filipino production
      ???
    - Diabla, 1978 (Mapcase-folder 14)
    - Le Diable est Parmi Nous, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 14)
      Poster includes advertisements for both The Posession of Virginia and The Exorcism of Hugh (Neither the Sea Nor the Sand)
      The Posession of Virginia
    - Davo u Mozgu, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Devil in the Brain
      Original Italian title: Il Diavolo nel Cervello
      Press sheets
    - Davo u Mozgu, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 24)
    - Il Diavolo nel Cervello, 1972; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 29)
    - La Muchacha en la Escoba, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      The Girl on the Broomstick
      Original Czech Title: Dívka na koštěti
    - Dívka na koštěti, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 15)